Carla Arrowsmith

carla.arrowsmith@gmail.com 07943932604

Portfolio https://carlasweb.github.io/portfolio.github.io/

Profile

I currently work full-time as a front-end web developer, and I am seeking alternative employment to further my skills and tech stack. I'm a passionate front-end web developer with a proven track record of nearly 3 years in the industry, specialising in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, and basic PHP. While my current role has exposed me to core coding languages I would like the opportunity to work more with modern frameworks. I am currently learning Vue.js and I am willing to learn any language/framework to succeed in my next role.

Key Skill

- · Web design & development
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Management/Team leader
- Good administration

- Able to achieve targets
- · Ability to learn new things
- Very hard worker
- Excellent customer service

Employment History

Junior front end web developer – CVP – July 2021 – current

CVP is a leading Broadcast and Professional video solutions providers in the United Kingdom and Europe. I work in the web development team, I design and develop the front-end elements of the main ecommerce website, smaller subsites and internal systems.

Project Administrator - Noved - September 2020 - July 2021

Noved is a project management company, I am currently working on the Tesco account for the electrical vehicle rollout. My role includes various administrative tasks and invoicing.

Guest relations and aftercare executive - Juliots Well Holiday park - July 2018 - September 2020

At Juliots Well Holiday Park my role included reception work and various administrative tasks, I manage the aftercare for new lodges and booking in engineers, organising the new developments and I also arranged maintenance and housekeeping jobs.

Paralegal - Toller Beattie LLP - Feb 2016 to July 2018

At Toller Beattie I was a paralegal, I assist in the commercial conveyancing department and I was secretary to the President of the Devon and Somerset Law Society.

Fertiliser Trader - Mole Valley Forage Services - Feb 2011 to Feb 2016

Mole Valley Forage was a sister company of Mole Valley Farmers that specialise in forage products such as minerals, fertilisers, and bedding treatments.

At Mole Valley Forage I started my role assisting clients with animal health, I would advise customers on mineral deficiencies and livestock health issues, I then moved onto a fertiliser trading role. In this role I looked after Devon and Cornwall and supplied fertiliser to our customers, I liaised with suppliers. I had a team of representatives out on the road that I supported, and I also dealt with administrative duties, customer service and supervised newer members of the team.

Telesales Manager - Absolute debt recovery - Jan 2009 to 2011

Absolute Debt Recovery is the leading debt recovery agency in the South West, on average gaining results of 80% in the recovery of debts.

I was the telesales manager of a team of 5 and my duties are to call businesses that might have debt recovery issues and arrange meetings with our representatives and support the sales team giving them areas to work in and help with any problems they may have and general admin work.

Various Roles - The Soap Kitchen - 2006 to 2009

At The Soap Kitchen, I had a lot of job roles as the company was quite small when I started and grew quite quickly, some of my duties were admin and office work, such as downloading orders, dealing with phone calls and emails

from customers and suppliers, stock control, filling and archiving customers' orders and personal info and various other paperwork. Out of the office, I did such things as making and designing the handmade soaps and various other toiletries I have also done the processing of orders and sometimes general warehouse work, I also supervised and trained new members of staff.

Education History

2018 – 2021 Plymouth University

• Foundation Degree in Computing

2013 Mainstream Computer Training Services

• Computer Technologies

2012 - 2013 Babcock NVQ Level 2

• Contact centre Level 2 including Maths and English

2006 - 2007 **NVQ2**

• Business and admin

2005 to 2006 Learndirect

- New CLAIT computer course
- Adult Maths Level 2
- Adult Literacy Level 2

1999 to 2004 Great Torrington School

G.C.S.E

- English D
- Maths C
- Science DD

Hobbies & Interests

In my spare time I enjoy wildlife photography and long walks, I like water sports and I enjoy surfing, when I am not out and about I like to read.

References

Available on request.